This is terrible, brother.
Yeah... I never thought it'd be this bad.
It's worse than what was reported to headquarters.
First, we need to hurry and find Lieutenant Havoc.
What is it, Al? It's hard to walk if you stick that close to me.
I'm just... not good with this kind of creepy atmosphere.
Huh?
What's with that? You're such a coward, Al.
Look at the Lieutenant. Even though she's a woman,
she doesn’t seem scared at all. She's like...
‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ WHOA!
Look at the Lieutenant. Even though she's a woman,
she doesn’t seem scared at all. She's like... WHOA!
‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ ‎ WHOA!
Look at the Lieutenant. Even though she's a woman,
she doesn’t seem scared at all. She's like... Whoa!
W-W-W-W-Wait, Lieutenant!
No, I didn't mean to insult you or anything! I just...
We're surrounded.
When did they get here?
Both of you, get ready! They're coming!